<Activity>
<Item><Question>Did you bring a movie to watched?</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To rest is all Victor wants to do. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Danielle left a while ago to visit the cemetery.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Would you like to swim after the sun goes down?</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>I approached Carl but he refused to talked to me. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>You need a towel to wash your self with. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Instead, Michael chose to staying behind with his friends. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Did Ryan really ask to be called first?</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>I can't believe Max agreed to help me with my homework. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Julia can't bear to stare at the dirty house. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Dan stopped quickly to studying the fish in the pond. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>I hope you have a book to read while we wait. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To taking deep breaths will help you calm down.</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>I  told Marie a hundred times. But she refuses to believe me. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To compares answers after the exam is no use. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Do you intend to submit this paper later?</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>There are dishes to wash in the kitchen. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Children like pretending to being adults. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To concentrate on the movie is hard to do. It's very long and slow. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Gill arranged to meeting with his friends tonight.</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>There are more cookies to eat on the table. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>My sister promised my parents to cook dinner tonight.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>The family decided to spending more time with each other. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To believe the story would be silly, wouldn't it?</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Richard gave Sam a ball to played with.</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>The group failed to realize that they were out of time.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To encourages Mimi is our plan right now. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>The letters ceased to arrive last month. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>It was then that Sandro started to run fast.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Are these clothes for me to wear?</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Ron was dreading to think of what will happen.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To increases our profit is our intention.</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Wayne attempted to shoot, but it missed. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Is that medicine for Leila to took later?</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To march with everyone at the parade was so much fun. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Brent expected to be done with his chores by afternoon.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Why don't you try to mingles with other people?</Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>Those crayons are not for you to waste.</Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>I'm sorry I failed to let everyone know about the changes. </Question><Answer>yes</Answer></Item>
<Item><Question>To observes is our teacher's job, not yours. </Question><Answer>no</Answer></Item>
</Activity>


